Biboo's here to play
(Yeah, uh huh, ah ah)
Let's go
Woke up in the morning
I had a funny dream
I was a stone that had been thrown
No way back, I was all in
(I was all in)
What if that was me soaring straight to the top?
Let's take a chance, game on and shoot my shot
Log in, get good, you mad? Let's cook
Talk beep, get hit, clean sweep, let's go
Now you know what's up
Hit 'em with a one-two-three, BIBOO BIBOO
Come and test your luck
Yeah we comin' in clutch, BIBOO BIBOO
Skipping stone in flight
Take 'em out one-shot, BIBOO BIBOO
Come and help me fight
Get on up, let's go, just me and you
Player one and player two
We'll see this through
Close my eyes, make a wish
One more shot, I will not miss
ROCK IN!
Bububa Bububu Ba
Bububa Bubu Yeah
Bububa Bambam Ba
Bububa Bumbum Ba
Bububa Bubu Yeah
Bububa Baba Ba
Bububu Bububu Bububu Ba
Level up, we go onwards
Aiming for another win
A diamond in the rough, it's kinda tough
You gotta keep on rollin'
(Gotta keep on rollin')
The grind goes on and on, no breaks
Seal the cracks with a few bandaids
I'll try over and over and over again
Just one more round, please?
Now you know what's up
Hit 'em with a one-two-three, BIBOO BIBOO
Come and test your luck
Yeah we comin' in clutch, BIBOO BIBOO
Skipping stone in flight
Take 'em out one-shot, BIBOO BIBOO
Come and help me fight
Get on up, let's go, just me and you
Player one and player two
We'll see this through
Close my eyes, make a wish
One more shot, I will not miss
ROCK IN!
Lost in this game, I feel the strain
But I'm pulled back up by your gravity
Your gravity
I see the shape, I feel the space
It's set in stone, carve it into me
I just wanna be Biboo
Now you know what's up
Hit 'em with a one-two-three, BIBOO BIBOO
Come and test your luck
Yeah we comin' in clutch, BIBOO BIBOO
Skipping stone in flight
Take 'em out one-shot, BIBOO BIBOO
Better hit quicksave 'cause
Biboo's here to play
Now you know what's up
Hit 'em with a one-two-three, BIBOO BIBOO
Come and test your luck
Yeah we comin' in clutch, BIBOO BIBOO
Skipping stone in flight
Take 'em out one-shot, BIBOO BIBOO
Come and help me fight
Get on up, let's go, just me and you
Player one and player two
We'll see this through
Close my eyes, make a wish
One more shot, I will not miss
ROCK IN!
Rock In!
BIBOO BIBOO!